Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Administrative Records, 1921-2010; 486757
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007; 486761 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - United States Green Building Council, 1999; 486760 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Waterfront Development Council, 1988; 486759 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "West-Fair" Decision: Task Force, 1995-1996; 486758 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Series III: General Files, 1918-2011; 486309
  Series III: General Files, 1918-2011 contains correspondence, publications, clippings, and other records. Material is mainly organized into subject files, notably on the New York City Building Code and charter revisions.
  - 42nd Street Development Project: Final Environmental Impact Statement (FEIS), 1984; 486756 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "1929 Amendments to the New York State Lien Law", 486755 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1954-1966; 486754 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1970-1977; 486753 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1986-1987; 486752 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - American Consulting Engineers Council, 1980; 486751 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - American Federation of Labor: Building and Construction Trades Bulletin, 1952; 486750 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - American Federation of Labor: Building Trades Department, 1968; 486749 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - American Institute of Architects: Founding History, 1957; 486748 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - American Institute of Architects: Suggested Guide to Bidding Procedure, 1959; 486747 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Articles (NYBC), 1980-1995; 486746 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Articles (NYBC), 2007, Undated; 486745 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Asbestos Control, 1986-1988; 486744 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Asbestos Control: Safe Buildings Alliance, 1984-1985; 486743 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Asbestos Control: Westat, inc. Report, 1987; 486742 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Asbestos Regulations, 1984-1987; 486741 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors, 1976; 486740 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors: Press Release, Undated; 486739 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Associated Builders and Owners of Greater New York: Anniversary Invitation, 1981; 486738 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Associated General Contractors of Minnesota (Pamphlet), Undated; 486737 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Barney, William Joshua: Address before New Jersey Building Congress, 1924; 486736 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Biographical: A-C, Various; 486735 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Biographical: D-F, Various; 486734 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Biographical: G-H, Various; 486733 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Biographical: I-L, Various; 486732 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Biographical: M-N, Various; 486731 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Biographical: O, Various; 486730 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Biographical: P, Various; 486729 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Biographical: R, Various; 486728 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Biographical: S, Various; 486727 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Biographical: T, Various; 486726 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Biographical: U, Various; 486725 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Biographical: V, Various; 486724 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Biographical: W, Various; 486723 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Biographical: Z, Various; 486722 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Brennan, Peter, 1971-1975; 486721 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1982; 486720 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council: Howard McSpedon Memorial, circa 1957; 486719 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Building Code, National, 1965; 486718 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Building Code, New York City, 1965-1966; 486717 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Building Code, New York City, 1967-1969; 486716 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Building Code, New York City: Charter Amendment, 1961; 486715 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1961-1962; 486714 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1963-1965; 486713 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1966; 486712 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1967; 486711 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1968-1969; 486710 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Building Code, New York City: Committee to Study Article L-1, 1965-1966; 486709 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1960-1962; 486708 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1963; 486707 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1964; 486706 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1965-1967; 486705 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Building Code, New York City: Public Hearing Statements, 1967-1968; 486704 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1959-1960; 486703 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1961; 486702 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1962; 486701 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1963; 486700 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1964; 486699 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1965; 486698 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1966; 486697 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1967; 486696 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1968; 486695 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Building Code, New York City: Publicity, 1969; 486694 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Building Code, New York City: Revisions, 1969-1973; 486693 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Building Industry Employers Association Convention, Dec 1952; 486692 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1979; 486691 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1980-1981; 486690 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Building Industry Employers Association: Legislative Committee, 1982-1983; 486689 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Building the City of the 21st Century (New York City Government), 1993; 486688 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Building Trade Employers Association, 1949, Undated; 486687 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1949; 486686 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1953; 486685 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Building Trade Employers Association: News and Opinion, 1986; 486684 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Building Owners' and Managers' Association of Greater New York: Newsletter, 1978; 486683 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Burns, Jeremiah, 1960-1967; 486682 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Business Committee on Midtown Traffic, 1986; 486681 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Business Council of New York State, inc., 1988-1989; 486680 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Business for Efficient Transportation: Press Release, Undated; 486679 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Business Marketing Corporation for New York City (Pamphlet), circa 1978; 486678 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Business Roundtable: Subjects of Bargaining, 1981; 486677 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Center for Construction Industry Studies, Proposal, 1979; 486676 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States: Congressional Action, 1978-1980; 486675 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Housing and Planning Council: The Assessor, 1986; 486674 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1962; 486673 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1968; 486672 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1972; 486671 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1977; 486670 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1979; 486669 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1980-1982; 486668 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1982-1985; 486667 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1986-1988; 486666 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1992; 486665 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1995; 486664 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1999; 486663 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, Undated; 486662 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Coalition for Equitable Construction Contracts, 1983; 486661 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Code of Ethics for the Building Industry: Exposition, Undated; 486660 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Columbia University: Manhattanville Expansion, Undated; 486659 (Box 11, Folder 16a)
  - Commercial Rent Control, 1986-1988; 486658 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Casino Gaming of New York City: "Case for Casino Gambling", 1981; 486657 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Community Planning Districts: History, Map, etc., 1968; 486656 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller Functions in New York City and in Other Jurisdictions: Report by H.D. Underhill, 1970; 486655 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Con Edison (Pamphlet), 1981; 486654 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Building Congress (Pamphlet), 1960; 486653 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Consolidated Carting Corporation, 1958; 486652 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Construction Coordinator, 1970; 486651 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Construction Cost Pamphlet, 1956; 486650 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Construction Cost Task Force, 1978; 486649 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Construction Cost Trend Report, 1949; 486648 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Construction Finance Manager's Association: "New York Construction Market in the 1990s", 1988; 486647 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Construction Industry Publicity Program Report [additional copy in oversize box 23], circa 1947; 486646 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Contract Settlements: Memo Draft, 1978; 486645 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Contractors: Eligibility Regulations, 1985; 486644 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Contractors: Performance Evaluations, 1986; 486643 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Corporate Codes of Conduct, 1990; 486642 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1930; 486641 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1954; 486640 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1958; 486639 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970; 486638 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1974; 486637 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976; 486636 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1977; 486635 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1978; 486634 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1979; 486633 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1980; 486632 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1981; 486631 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1982; 486630 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1983; 486629 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985; 486628 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1986; 486627 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1986; 486626 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1987; 486625 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Apr-Aug 1987; 486624 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1987; 486623 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1988; 486622 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1988; 486621 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1989; 486620 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1989; 486619 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1989; 486618 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1990; 486617 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1990; 486616 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1991; 486615 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1993; 486614 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1994; 486613 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1995; 486612 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, Mar-Jun 1995; 486611 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Sep 1995; 486610 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1995; 486609 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1996; 486608 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Apr-Jun 1996; 486607 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1996; 486606 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1999; 486605 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2007; 486604 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Undated; 486603 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Position Letters, 2002-2007; 486602 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Position Letters, 2008-2009; 486601 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Courter, Joseph, Various; 486600 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Crane Regulations, 1970; 486599 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Decision '89" (NYBC), 1989; 486598 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Discrimination in New York City Construction Trades (Report, New York City Commission on Human Rights), 1993; 486597 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Edifice, 1960-1965; 486596 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Edifice, 1970-1977; 486595 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Edifice, 1980-1982; 486594 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Electrical Code, 1967; 486593 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Electricity Outlook, 2001, 2006; 486592 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Eller, Peter W. "Teamwork in Building" ( Elks Magazine), 1948; 486591 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ellis Island Medal of Honor, 1994; 486590 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - (e)Update, 2003-2007; 486589 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Exploring Economic Development Opportunities in Recycling, 1993; 486588 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act As Amended (Bureau of National Affairs), 1949; 486587 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Federal City Council: Annual Report, 1994; 486586 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank of Seattle (Pamphlet), 1979; 486585 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1971; 486584 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Fenner Memorial Fund, 1927; 486583 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Forum Club, 1995; 486582 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Fouilhoux, J. Andre (President, NYBC): Death Announcement and Tribute, 1945; 486581 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Grand Central Station Renovation, 1987; 486580 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Gun Hill Road Retail Development, 1995; 486579 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Harbour Village Housing Project, 1970-1972; 486578 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "History of the Inception of the Congress Movement" (Kohn), circa 1924; 486577 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Holden, Thomas: Address to the Chicago Building Congress, 1938; 486576 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Home Improvement, 1968; 486575 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Housing Maintenance Code, 1967-1969; 486574 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Hudson River Project: Water Tunnel #3, 1977-1980; 486573 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Hult, Eugene E.: Fellowship Fund, 1968; 486572 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - ICONN Project: New York Waterway and Port Modernization, 1977; 486571 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - "Impact of Insurance Issues on New York City's Construction Industry", 2004; 486570 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Index of Construction Contract Value (1921-1970), 1971; 486569 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Industry Promotion Fund, 1992-1993; 486568 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Institute of Public Administration: Contracting in New York City Government, 1987; 486567 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Transportation Systems, City University of New York: Private Sector in Public Transportation in New York City (Draft), 1990; 486566 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - "Jobs and Economic Regeneration in New York City (Business/Labor Working Group), circa 1976; 486565 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Jordan, Vernon, 1973; 486564 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Legislation: Battery Park City Authority, 1973; 486563 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Legislation: City Housing Authority Law, 1957-1958; 486562 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Legislation: Community Development Amendment, 1971; 486561 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Legislation: Construction Superintendents, 1960-1969; 486560 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Legislation: Construction Waste Fees, 1973; 486559 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Legislation: Correspondence, 1974, 1982-1983; 486558 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Legislation: Department of Buildings Fee Increases, 1969; 486557 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Legislation: Department of Buildings (New), 1972; 486556 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Legislation: Energy Conservation Bill, 1973-1974; 486555 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Legislation: Engineering, 1968; 486554 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Legislation: Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1986; 486553 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Legislation: Height of Buildings, 1967; 486552 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Legislation: High Rise Law, 1982; 486551 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Legislation: Internal Revenue Service Proposals (Long-Term Contracts), 1972; 486550 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Legislation: Kalisch-Jarcho Bill, 1983-1984; 486549 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Labor Reform Act, 1977; 486548 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Lobbying Bill, 1972; 486547 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Noise Code, 1983; 486546 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Noise Control Code, 1971-1973; 486545 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Wicks Law, 1987; 486544 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1984-1989; 486543 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1990-1996; 486542 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the Editor, 2000-2006; 486541 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor, Undated; 486540 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Lindsay, John V., 1967; 486539 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Literature Requests: "Recommendations on 'or Equal Clause'", Jun 1963; 486538 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Literature Requests: "Recommendations on 'or Equal Clause'", Jul 1963-Mar 1964; 486537 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1963-1965; 486536 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1966-1969; 486535 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mall at Rego Park, 1986; 486534 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - "Mandate Millstone" (Mayor Koch Statement at U.S. Conference of Mayors), Jan 1980; 486533 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - "Market Letter: A Digest of Construction Markets & Trends", 1962-1963; 486532 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mayoral Committees, 1992; 486531 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Reorganization of New York City Government, 1967; 486530 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Reorganization of New York City Government, 1967; 486529 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City, 1967; 486528 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City, 1968; 486527 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Measurement of the Size and Importance of the Construction Industry in the Economy of New York City: Correspondence, 1966-1967; 486526 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Metrobuild, 1987; 486525 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Metrobuild, 1988-1989; 486524 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Minority Gains in New York Construction Jobs (Pamphlet), 1979; 486523 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - MIUS Forum, 1980; 486522 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Moses, Robert, 1965-1978; 486521 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Municipal Services Administration, 1968; 486520 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - National Asbestos Council, 1989; 486519 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - National Association of Women in Construction, 1982; 486518 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - National Building Museum Award Dinner, 1989; 486517 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - National Bureau of Standards, 1968; 486516 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - National Congress of the Building and Construction Industry, 1929-1936; 486515 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - National Construction Employers Council, 1982; 486514 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - National Federation of Building Industries, 1918; 486513 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - National Institute of Building Sciences, 1982, 1986; 486512 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - New Buildings: Cost, 1964; 486511 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - New Jersey Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1986; 486510 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New York Alliance for the Public Schools, 1989; 486509 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - New York Association of Consulting Engineers, 1982-1991; 486508 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - NYBC History, 1924-1984, Undated; 486507 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - NYBC News, 1933-1945; 486506 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - NYBC News, 1950-1951; 486505 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NYBC News, 1955; 486504 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - "New York Building Trades," Chapter 4 of Trade Unionism and Labor Problems, John R. Commons, Undated; 486503 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - New York Carpenters Labor-Management: Reception for A. D'Amato, Feb 17, 1995; 486502 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1965; 486501 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce: Great New York City Turnaround Begins, 1978; 486500 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - New York Chamber of Commerce: History, 1967; 486499 (Box 13, Folder 50a)
  - New York City Board of Standards and Appeals, 1957; 486498 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - New York City Board of Standards and Appeals, 1975; 486497 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - New York City Building Code Commission, 1970; 486496 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - New York City Bureau of Labor Services, 1980-1981; 486495 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - New York City: Capital Commitments, 1990; 486494 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - New York City Capital Projects, 1979-1989, 486493 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Alliance for a Better Charter, 1989; 486492 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Contracting and Procurement, Undated; 486491 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Property Management, Undated; 486490 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Charter Provisions on Public Construction, Undated; 486489 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - New York City Charter Revision: The Charter Review, 1987-1989; 486488 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Clippings, 1987-1989; 486487 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Contracting and Procurement for City Goods, Services and Construction, 1989; 486486 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Correspondence, 1987-1989; 486485 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Land Governance and the New York City Charter, 1988; 486484 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Land Governance and the New York City Charter (Volume 2), 1988; 486483 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Neighborhoods, Land Use and the New York City Charter, 1987; 486482 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York City Charter Revision: NYBC Proposals and Statements, 1987-1989; 486481 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter, 1985-1987; 486480 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, 1987-1989; 486479 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Chair's Recommendations, 1989; 486478 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Initial Proposals, 1988; 486477 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Meeting Notices, 1988-1989; 486476 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Preliminary Proposals, 1989; 486475 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Press Releases, 1988-1989; 486474 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposal Summaries, 1988; 486473 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposal Summaries, 1989; 486472 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Proposals, 1989; 486471 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - New York City Charter Revision: New York City Charter Revision Commission, Publications, 1988-1989; 486470 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Proposals and Statements, 1988-1989; 486469 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Proposed Charter, 1989; 486468 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - New York City Charter Revision: State Charter Revision Commission for New York City, 1975; 486467 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New York City Charter Revision: Testimony, 1989; 486466 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New York City Civil Defense: Emergency Equipment Survey, 1958; 486465 (Box 14, Folder 28)